♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Thanks for driving me to the
library for story time, Brian.
Today we're reading The
Very Hungry Caterpillar
vs. The Human Centipede.
I heard it's like Alien vs. Predator.
With a little bit more butt eating.
That does sound fun,
but what if I took you
- to a different library today?
- What?
But I like my library. I
met Curious George there.
Mom said he was a puppet,
but she's stupid.
I'm just saying we
should go to the library
at Quahog University
and take your education
to a higher level.
I guess I can try it. I mean,
I do want to get ahead.
I don't want to end up like
Meg, doing sad one-woman shows.
♪ Oh, I love trash ♪
♪ Anything dirty or dingy or dusty ♪
♪ Anything ragged or rotten or rusty ♪
♪ Yes, I love trash... ♪
Whose fault is this?
You're wearing a garbage bag as a cape.
Who do you think?
- Him?
- Shh. She's crushing it!
Oh, yeah. That's good library.
Aw, you didn't come here for
me; you came to be a creep.
Whatever. You go do your thing.
I'm gonna go watch that young
hotshot attorney over there
who's clearly in the
middle of a movie montage.
Oh! He found it.
He's gonna win the case.
Oh, no. It was a '70s movie.
- So, who you reading?
- George Eliot.
Ah, Georgie.
I'm a big fan.
- I think he, uh...
- She.
She said it best when she said...
"Bantam Press, 1851."
- Lumineers?
- What?
Hmm?
You just said "Lumineers"
with no context.
Did I do that?
Ugh!
Tumblr?
Wow, I've never seen someone go
oh for six in 15 minutes before.
Just hard rejection
after hard rejection.
- What's going on over there?
- Looks like a student rally.
They probably forgot
to study for an exam,
so they organized a protest.
In the '90s, you'd just
pull a fire alarm...
Now you hold a protest.
That is, when they're not
looking down at their phones.
Hey, what's going on?
Someone wrote "weird" on
the transgender bathroom,
and the school president
didn't overreact,
so we want him fired!
Seems reasonable.
Exactly!
Oh, I see news cameras.
I'm gonna yell "Viva la Stool"
like a young, white drunkard.
And last week, a professor told
his class to have a nice day,
which is microaggression,
because in our systemic rape culture
no day is a nice day.
So we want him fired, too.
Hey, if you
don't want to get fired,
- don't become a teacher, right?
- Totally.
You should tweet that. #FireEveryone.
Viva la Stool!
Well, I guess I could
fire up my account again.
All right, open app.
Got a bunch of those. No biggie.
Typing tweet.
Blast off in three,
two, one,
and tweeted.
I am back in the game. See?
Oop, you're gone.
And the crowd is gone.
And the animators are gone.
Hey, Stewie, what do you
think about this tweet?
Oh, don't be that guy.
"Kelly Ripa no-shows at work."
Who does she think she is,
a Republican senator?
#G-O-P-U.
Three references in one
tweet. I'm sweating.
I'll just add it to my notes for later.
Why are you getting into Twitter now?
Unless you're an athlete or
a celebrity, no one cares.
A lot of people like my stuff.
Oh, yeah? Someone needs
to tell Donald Trump
it's not fashionable
to wear orange on your
face after Labor Day.
#OompaTrumpa.
Zero retweets. Zero likes.
- Yeah, viral.
- You know, I don't care.
You can't stop me. Just like people
can't stop Peter from
ordering shepherd's pie.
And what can I get for you, sir?
I'll have the shepherd's pie.
I'm sorry, but that's not on the menu.
- Well, do you have potatoes?
- Yes.
- Butter?
- Cream?
- Yes.
- Salt?
- Pepper?
- Yes.
- Garlic?
- Onions?
- Yes.
- Lamb?
- Carrots?
- Yes.
- Eggs?
- Flour?
- Yes.
- Rosemary?
- Thyme?
- Yes.
- Chicken broth?
- Corn?
- Yes.
- Peas?
Lightsaber?
Remember when we did Star Wars?
Better get a tweet out before
I go dark for a few hours.
About to see the new Kevin Hart movie.
Just kidding. I'm white
and went to college.
#BaywatchMovie.
Wow, I haven't seen that much camel toe
since the Arab Spring.
#ThinkingInTweets.
Nah.
Hey, are you @dogbackwards from Twitter?
I am. Are-are you a fan?
You racist jerk!
I hope you get foot-and-mouth disease!
What the hell was that?
Uh-oh.
Wow,
you are blowing up!
Blowing up bad.
Ah, look at that... Huffington
Post just picked it up.
Buckle up, buddy.
- There he is!
- Where? I'm in the back.
Hey, how was Baywatch? I
want to see that bad.
What were you thinking,
writing that tweet?
What? It was just a joke.
Brian, it's not 2005...
You can't just go online
and say whatever you want.
Yeah, remember how mad people
got when DiGiorno tweeted
about domestic violence?
And they're not even a
guy. They're pizza.
All right, all right,
I'll delete the tweet.
You haven't deleted it yet?
What a train wreck!
There. Done. Done.
See? It's done. It's gone.
What about all those people outside?
They'll see that I deleted it,
and it'll all blow over. Trust me.
I hope so, but you never know.
They're still pretty mad at me
down at Dick's Sporting Goods.
Um, what's the name of this place?
Dick's.
A-And what's that say on your shirt?
Can I have two balls... and a helmet?
Hey, you're the guy from the phone.
Start the car, Chris!
- Did you get him, Dad?
- We got him!
Hey, Sid. Happy Mango Monday.
Hmm.
Hmm. Those nighttime
information technology classes
must really be getting to Sid.
Hey, Curt.
Hmm.
Curt? Come on, it's me,
Lunchtime Lois.
Gil, help me out here.
Hmm!
Gil, no! Uh, what about
Barbara? Is she back there?
She can clear this up.
Let me talk to Barbara.
She doesn't want to talk to you, either.
Nobody does...
Not as long as you're living
with that racist dog.
Oh, come on!
It was just a bad joke.
Where's Stanley?
He'll vouch for me. Let
me talk to Stanley.
Or Henry. Somebody help me out here.
- Chip?
- Hmm!
- Karen?
- JJ?
- Hmm.
- Angela?
- Tito?
- Hmm!
- Larry?
You can't freeze me out like this.
We're on a first-name basis!
They're on our name tags, Lois.
But I don't even have
to look!
I don't even have to look!
Hey, how come no one told me
we were going to the Clam?
Hey, Jerome, give me a beer.
Oh, why? 'Cause I'm, like, your slave?
Man, you're no better
than your racist dog.
Come on, man.
B-Brian was just making a joke.
I told you about Brian. I told you.
Come on, he deleted his tweet.
But the hurt has been
RT'd in our hearts.
Peter, you better get out of here
before I start saying "sir" like a cop.
- Come on, Joe, I...
- Sir? Sir?
You've been asked to leave.
- Joe, it's me, Peter. I...
- Sir.
I don't want to have to ask you again.
- Please leave.
- All right, fine.
- Sir!
- No, Joe, Joe.
- He's leaving.
- Sir!
- Joe, Joe...
- He's gone.
- Sir.
- It's okay.
He's gone.
Your dog wrote an insensitive tweet.
You can't eat here.
Uh-oh, Meg. It's a sensitivity mob.
It was just a joke.
There's no such thing as jokes anymore.
Yeah, we live in a post-joke world.
Chris, maybe we should just eat outside.
No, Meg, we're eating here.
I'd like to see you try.
It was... a joke.
Can you put on the Canucks game?
No, go away.
Loser.
This is getting out of control.
We can't leave the house
without getting harassed.
Yeah, yesterday I went outside
to try to get the mail
and I had a seizure.
That may not be protester-related,
but still, you got to
do something, Brian.
What do you want me to do?
I-I deleted my Twitter
account, my Instagram,
Facebook, everything.
People still won't leave me alone.
You have to apologize.
Go outside, do it now.
Tell them that it was a
mistake and how sorry you are
and maybe they'll get off our backs.
Maybe you're right.
I got to face them and
hope they'll forgive me.
Hello.
As you all know, I'm Brian Griffin.
Boo.
Boo, Brian Griffin. Boo.
I want to read a few words...
Boo. Liar.
Boo, Brian Griffin, boo.
Anyway, I-I want to...
Boo. Apologize somewhere else.
Boo. Boo, Brian, boo.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm
here today to apologize...
Why did you say "ladies" first?
That's sexist.
It's just, it's just
a-a standard greeting.
Let-let me start over.
Gentlemen and ladies...
Ooh, says the man.
Okay, sorry, I-I... Um,
humans in the audience...
I identify as a basketball.
Humans and basketballs...
I'm a parrot who mimics words
but doesn't comprehend them.
Humans, basketballs, talking parrots,
and-and whatever else is out there...
"Whatever"? It's whoever.
Actually, it's whomever.
No one likes you, Mary.
All right, all right,
just-just calm down, okay?
Now you're tone policing us!
That makes me uncomfortable.
Anything that makes me
uncomfortable in 2017
should be illegal.
You know what? (BLEEP) you.
I'm not a racist, all right?
I just told a bad joke.
There's a huge difference.
But nobody on the Internet
ever takes the time
to ask themselves, "Is this
worth freaking out over?"
Or, "Are there bigger problems
in the world than this tweet?"
Well, I assure you, there are.
And just for the record,
I love black people.
I watch tons of black porn.
So, what do you all want from me, huh?
You-you want to ruin my life?
Then congratulations. You did it.
Everybody hates me.
I can't leave the house
without getting harassed.
No one will hire me.
That was a problem before.
I can't turn on my phone
without strangers telling me
to kill myself or that they're
gonna kill my family.
Leave me alone!
I'm the self-righteous,
liberal douchebag, not you!
I've kissed a transsexual before!
How many of you can say that?!
Where's my (BLEEP) medal?!
I am so far left,
I'm spinning in circles, you (BLEEP).
Instead of killing myself,
I should kill all of you!
I'd like to see you try.
Ow! Jeez.
Well, we started the dialogue.
You screamed "black porn"
at the top of your lungs
in front of women and children.
I am not the person those
people out there say I am.
I know that, but you
also haven't done much
to prove that you aren't.
I know, I know.
All I have left is you guys.
Thank God you have my back.
- We think you should move out.
- What?!
Oh! Brian, listen, we love you,
but they're throwing
things at our house.
We've got to keep our family safe.
I'm sorry. It's for the best.
Are you serious?!
You're okay with this?!
Does this slow pan across
our disapproving faces
answer your question?
I saw Baywatch.
That thing was frickin' rad.
I still think this is a drastic measure.
Yeah, I messed up,
but what about all the
stupid things Peter's done?
He's never been kicked
out and his life...
My life is not the issue here.
Peter, calm down.
Did you eat breakfast this morning?
I had a banana and a coffee.
Why am I so fat?
I'm sorry, Brian, but this
is the way it has to be.
All right, then.
I guess this is good-bye.
Brian, wait.
This collar is ours.
It has our address on it.
Peace, dude.
All right, radio, time for you
to tell me what this all means.
♪ I got a pocket full of quarters ♪
♪ And I'm headed to the arcade ♪
♪ I don't have a lot of money ♪
♪ But I'm bringing ev'rything I made ♪
♪ I've got a callus on my finger ♪
♪ And my shoulder's hurting, too ♪
♪ I'm gonna eat them all up ♪
♪ Just as soon as they turn blue ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got Pac-Man fever ♪
♪ Pac-Man fever ♪
♪ It's driving me crazy ♪
♪ Driving me crazy ♪
♪ I've got Pac-Man fever ♪
♪ Pac-Man fever ♪
♪ I'm going out of my mind. ♪
Hey. Are you here for the Time magazines
with some of the letters cut out?
Uh, no, I... no, I saw that you
have an apartment for rent.
Okay.
Here. Apartment 23.
Oh, okay.
I just have one rule here:
no kissing the mailman.
I don't think that's gonna be a problem.
You haven't seen him,
so don't say that yet.
Mail's here.
Wow.
If I have other
items I want to buy,
uh, can I buy them here
at the pharmacy window?
Yes.
Ruth? Yeah,
bring it over here.
We can buy them over here.
Where are you?
By the pharmacy.
Hang on, I'm
picking out sunscreen.
Sir, do you
mind if I go ahead of you?
Uh, yes, I do mind.
♪ This time I have really
lead myself astray... ♪
♪ Wrong way on a one-way track ♪
♪ Seems like I should
be getting somewhere ♪
♪ Somehow I'm neither
here nor there... ♪
Six dollars?
Hey, did you knock over a
few bottles in aisle seven?
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
Patricia?
Where's the big nail clipper?
I don't know.
Did you get rid of it?
Why would I get rid
of the big nail clipper?
'Cause you're a bitch, that's why.
Nice. Yeah, now I'm
gonna tell you where it is.
I knew you knew
where it was, you liar.
Tell me where it is!
No. Find it yourself.
Oh, okay. Fine.
How about I hide something
of yours?! Huh?!
Put that back!
No, tell me where
the big nail clipper is!
Boom.
Damn it.
Why can't you
use the little nail clipper?
I want
the big one, okay?!
And I don't want you using it anymore!
Shut up, little man!
You shut up!
Where'd you put it, you liar?!
- $900.
- "L."
- "R."
- Aw.
Two "R" s.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru